Guide to the Group Research, Inc. Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Topical Files
  - Quotations (Box 276)
  - Rabb Charitable Foundation, Sidney and Esther (Box 276)
  - Racial Studies Committee (Box 276)
  - Racism (Box 276)
  - Rader, Paul (Rev.) (Box 276)
  - Radford, Arthur W. (Admiral) (Box 276)
  - Radio Church of God (Box 276)
  - Radio Free America (Box 277)
  - Radio Free Europe Financial (Box 277)
  - Radio Free Europe (Box 277)
  - Radio Liberty Commmittee, Inc. New York, NY (Box 277)
    [Formerly American Committee for Liberation, Inc.]
  - Rafferty, Max (Dr.) Speeches and writings, Sacramento, CA (Box 277)
    [Author and right-wing activist See also the Group Research directory under Maxwell Lewis Rafferty, Jr.]
  - Rafferty, Max (Dr.), Sacramento, CA (Box 277)
  - "Rally" (Box 277)
  - Ralston Purina Company (Box 277)
  - Rampart College, Colorado Springs, CO and Santa Ana, CA (Box 277)
    [Rampart College is an enlargement on and extension of Freedom School. See also Freedom School and the Group Research directory under Freedom School and Rampart College.]
  - "Ramparts" (Box 277)
  - Ramsey, Ronald B. (Box 277)
  - Rand, Ayn (Box 278)
    [Author and proponent of "Objectivism" See also Objectivism and the Group Research directory under Ayn Rand.]
  - Rand, Clayton (Box 278)
  - Rand Corporation (Box 278)
  - Randall, Clarence B. (Box 278)
  - "Rank and File" (Box 278)
  - Rankin, James Lee (Box 278)
  - Rankin, Ronald (Box 278)
  - Ransburg, Harold P. (Box 278)
  - Ranuzzi, Frank X. (Mr. and Mrs.), Los Angeles, CA (Box 278)
    [Proprietors, Poor Richard's Book Shop See also Poor Richard's Book Shop and the Group Research directory under Mrs. and Mrs. Frank X. Ranuzzi and "The Death of Joe McCarthy: A Tribute and a Revelation" (a book by Ranuzzi).]
  - Rarick, John (Rep.), R-LA, 1970 (Box 278)
  - Rarick, John (Rep.), R-LA, 1969 (Box 278)
  - Rarick, John (Rep.), R-LA, 1968 (Box 278)
  - Rarick, John (Rep.), R-LA, 1967 (Box 279)
  - Rat Finks (Box 279)
  - Read, Leonard E. (Box 279)
  - "Reader's Digest" "Congressional Record" clippings (Box 279)
    [See also the Group Research directory under "Reader's Digest."]
  - "Reader's Digest" General (Box 279)
  - "Reader's Digest" Newspaper and magazine clippings (Box 279)
  - "Reader's Digest" Reprint (Box 279)
  - Reader's Digest Foundation (Box 279)
  - Reading Reform Foundation (Box 280)
  - Reagan, Maureen (Box 280)
    [Daughter of Ronald Reagan]
  - "Realist, The" (Box 280)
  - Realpolitical Institute (Box 280)
  - Reapportionment (Box 280)
  - Reardon, Leo F. (Box 280)
  - Reason Foundation (Box 280)
  - Rees, John (Box 280)
  - Reformed Drunks (Box 280)
  - Regan, Donald T. (Box 280)
  - Regent Foundation (Box 280)
  - Regnery Company (Box 280)
  - Regnery, W. H. (Box 280)
    [Former editor, "The Individualist" See also Intercollegiate Society of Individualists and Frank Chodorov.]
  - Regular Veterans Association of the United States (Box 281)
  - "Regulation" (Box 281)
  - Rehnquist, William H. (Chief Justice) (Box 281)
  - Religion and Cults, 1991- (Box 281)
  - Religion and Cults (Box 281)
  - Religion and Politics -- General (Box 281)
  - Religion and Society, Inc. (Box 281)
  - Religion -- Miscellaneous (Box 281)
  - Religious Book Club, Inc. (Box 282)
  - Religious Freedom Committee (Box 282)
  - Religious Heritage of America, Inc. (Box 282)
  - Religious Liberty Association of America (Box 282)
  - Religious Roundtable, 1982 (Box 282)
  - Religious Roundtable (Box 282)
  - Relm Foundation (Box 282)
  - "Remnant, The" (Box 282)
  - Rentschler, William H. (Box 282)
  - "Report" (Box 282)
  - "Report to the People" (Box 282)
  - Republic Communications Corporation (Box 282)
  - Republic Steel Corporation Educational and Charitable Trust (Box 282)
  - Republican Associates (Box 282)
  - Republican Committee of One Hundred, Inc. (Box 282)
  - Republican Congressional Committee (Box 282)
  - Republican Convention -- Delegate lists, 1964 (Box 283)
  - Republican Convention, 1964 (Box 283)
  - Republican Coordinating Committee (Box 283)
  - Republican Legislative Research Association (Box 283)
  - Republican Minute Men, Tulsa, OK (Box 283)
  - Republican National Committee (Box 283)
    [See also Right Wing -- Newspaper clippings.]
  - Republican Party, 1993- (Box 283)
  - Republican Party, 1988-92 (Box 283)
  - Republican Party, 1978- (Box 284)
  - Republican Party, 1969 (Box 284)
  - Republican Party, 1968 (Box 284)
  - Republican Party, 1967 (Box 284)
  - Republican Party, 1966 (Box 284)
    [See also Nelson A. Rockefeller and Series 1 and 2 -- Barry Goldwater.]
  - Republican Party, November 1964-5 (Box 284)
    [See also the Republican National Committee.]
  - Republican Party, 1964 (Box 285)
    [See also Series 3 -- New Mexico and Oklahoma.]
  - Republican Party 1964 Campaign (Box 285)
  - Republican Party, 1963 (Box 285)
    [See also Series 3 -- Texas.]
  - Republican Party, 1961-2 (Box 285)
  - Republican Party National Federation of Republican Women (Box 285)
  - Republican Party Republican Congressional Committee Newsletter (Box 285)
  - Republican Party Task Forces (Box 285)
  - Republican Party Teen Age Republicans (TAR) (Box 285)
  - Republican Party Women's National Republican Campaign Committee (Box 285)
  - Republican Policy Committee (Box 285)
  - "Republican Record" (Box 285)
  - Republicans for Progress (Box 285)
  - "Republimerican Retort, The" (Box 285)
  - Research -- Government (Box 286)
  - Research Associates (Box 286)
  - Research Group, Inc. (Box 286)
  - Research Institute of America (Box 286)
  - Research Institute on Communist Strategy and Propaganda (Box 286)
  - Responsible Government for America Foundation (Box 286)
  - Restore School Voluntary Prayer (RSVP) (Box 286)
  - Retired Officers Assocation of the United States (Box 286)
  - Reuther, Walter (Box 286)
  - "Revelator, The", Laguna Beach, CA (Box 286)
  - "Revere, The" (Box 286)
  - Revere Press (Box 286)
  - Revolutionary Action Movement (RAM) (Box 286)
  - Reyes, Manolo (Dr.) (Box 286)
  - Reynolds, Don Buck (Box 286)
  - Reynolds, William Bradford (Box 286)
  - Rhatican, Bill (Box 286)
  - Rhodes, John J. (Rep.), R-AZ (Box 286)
  - Rhodes Scholars (Box 286)
  - Rhodesia, 1979- (Box 286)
  - Rhodesia (Box 286)
  - Rhodesian Information Office Rhodesia (Box 287)
  - Dean Richards, Inc. Richards, Dean J. Bensenville, IL (Box 287)
    [Right-wing activist associated with the Cardinal Mindszenty Foundation and the Flick-Reedy Education Enterprises among others. See also the Group Research directory under Dean J. Richards.]
  - Richardson Foundation, The (Box 287)
    [See also F. Clifton White.]
  - Richardson, H. L. "Bill" (Sen.), R-CA (Box 287)
  - Richardson, Warren (Box 287)
  - Richfield Oil (Box 287)
  - Rickenbacker, Edward V. (Capt.), New York, NY (Box 287)
    [War hero and right-wing activist See also Right Wing -- General, NIC, and Fred G. Clark as well as the Group Research directory under Capt. Edward V. Rickenbacker.]
  - Rickenbacker, William F. (Box 287)
    [Son of Capt. Edward Rickenbacker Former Editor, "National Review" and right-wing activist See also the Group Research directory under William F. Rickenbacker.]
  - Rickover, Hyman G. (Admiral) (Box 287)
  - Riesel, Victor (Box 287)
  - "Right" (Box 287)
  - Right Brigade, The (Box 287)
  - "Right Report, The" (Box 287)
    [Later known as "The New Right Report."]
  - Right Rights Association of the United States (Box 287)
  - Resource Center, The (Box 286)
  - Right-To-Work -- General, 1977- (Box 287)
  - Right-To-Work -- General (Box 288)
    [See also Labor Digest, Chamber of Commerce, and National Right-To-Work Committee as well as Series 2 -- Right-To-Work.]
  - Right-To-Write Committee (Box 288)
  - Right Wing Book Club (Box 288)
  - Right Wing International (Box 288)
  - Ringer, Robert J. (Box 288)
  - Riots -- Race, student, and others (Box 288)
  - Ripon Society Miscellaneous, 1972- (Box 288)
  - Ripon Society Miscellaneous (Box 288)
  - Ripon Society "Ripon Forum" (Box 288)
  - "Ripsaw, The" (Box 289)
  - Riseley, James, P. (Lt.Gen.) (Box 289)
  - Ritterbush, Jacob H. (Box 289)
  - Rivers, L. Mendel (Rep.), D-SC (Box 289)
  - Rizzo, Frank (Box 289)
  - Roanridge Rural Training Foundation (Box 289)
  - Robb, Charles S. (Sen.), D-VA (Box 289)
  - Robb, Inez (Box 289)
  - "Robber's Roost" (Box 289)
  - Roberts, Alex M. (Box 289)
  - Roberts, Arch E. (Major), Fort Collins, CO, 1974- (Box 289)
    [Author and activist See also the Group Research directory under Major Archibald E. Roberts and under "Victory Denied" (a book by Roberts).]
  - Roberts, Arch E. (Major) (Box 289)
  - Roberts, Charles Kenneth (Box 289)
  - Roberts, George A. (Box 289)
  - Roberts, James C. (Box 289)
  - Roberts, Oral (Box 289)
    [See also Oral Roberts University.]
  - Roberts University, Oral, Tulsa, OK (Box 289)
    [See also Oral Roberts.]
  - Roberts, Paul Craig (Box 290)
  - Robertson, Kenneth D., Jr. (Box 290)
  - Robertson, Pat (Box 346)
    [See also Christian Coalition and the Christian Broadcasting Network.]
  - Robineau, M. H. (Box 290)
    [Major stockholder in Frontier Refining Company.]
  - Robinett, Paul M. (Box 290)
  - Robinhood Society of America (Box 290)
  - Robnett, George Washington, Pasadena, CA (Box 290)
    [Former director, Institute for Special Research Founder, Church League of America See also Church League of America, the Institute for Special Research, and the Group Research directory under George Washington Robnett.]
  - Roche, George C. (Box 290)
  - Roche, John P. (Box 290)
  - Rock Island Refining Corporation (Box 290)
  - Rock Report (Box 290)
    [See also Phoenix Study.]
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Box 290)
    [See also Series 1 and 2 -- Barry Goldwater and the Conservative Society of America.]
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. Campaign (Box 290)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. Friends (Box 290)
  - Rockford College, Rockford, IL (Box 290)
  - Rockwell, Willard F. (Col.) (Box 290)
    [See also Citizens Foreign Aid Committee.]
  - Rockwell, Willard F., Jr. (Box 290)
  - Roepke, Wilhelm (Box 290)
  - Rogers, Donald L. (Box 290)
  - Rogers, Paul (Rep.), D-FL (Box 290)
  - Rogers, Sherman (Box 290)
  - Rogge, Benjamin (Dr.) (Box 290)
  - Rohrbacher, Dana (Rep.), R-CA (Box 290)
  - Rojas, Sergio (Box 290)
  - "Roll Call" (Box 290)
  - Roller, W. E. (Box 290)
  - Rollman, Heinz (Box 290)
  - Roloff, Lester (Rev.) (Box 290)
  - Romfi (Box 290)
  - Romney, George, 1968 (Box 291)
  - Romney, George, 1966-7 (Box 291)
  - Romney, George, 1962-5 (Box 291)
    [See also Mormon Church.]
  - Romualdi, Serafino (Box 291)
    [See also American Institute for Free Labor Development.]
  - Ronthelym Charitable Trust, Boston, MA (Box 291)
  - Rooke, Allen D. (Box 291)
  - Roosevelt, Archibald B. (Box 291)
  - Roosevelt, Edith Kermit (Box 291)
  - Roosevelt, Kermit (Box 291)
  - Root, E. Merrill (Dr.), Thompson, CT (Box 291)
    [Former professor of English, Earlham College, Indiana as well as author and contributor to several right-wing publications See also Harding College, America's Future, Citizens Foreign Relations Committee, and the Group Research directory under Dr. E. Merrill Root and "Collectivism on the Campus" (a book by Root).]
  - Rosamary Foundation, New Orleans, LA (Box 291)
  - Rosenblatt, Maurice (Box 291)
  - Rosenstiel Foundation, Dorothy and Lewis (Box 291)
  - Ross, Seton (Box 291)
  - Rothbard, Murray N. (Box 291)
  - Roundtree, Martha (Box 291)
  - Rousselot, John H. (Rep.), R-CA (Box 291)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Rep. John H. Rousselot.]
  - Rowe, David (Dr.) (Box 292)
  - Royal Rangers (Box 292)
  - Royce, Scott Information from (Box 292)
  - Rozek, Edward J. (Dr.) (Box 292)
  - Rubicon Foundation, Inc. (Box 292)
  - Rudd, Augustin G. (Box 292)
    [Associated with the Sons of the American Revolution.]
  - Rudd, Eldon (Rep.), R-AZ (Box 292)
  - Ruff, Howard J. (Box 292)
  - Rukeyser, Louis (Box 292)
  - Rumely, Edward A. (Box 292)
  - Rumph, Mal (Dr.), Fort Worth, TX (Box 292)
    [Former President, Association of American Physicians and Surgeons See also the Group Research directory under Dr. Mal Rumph.]
  - Rumsfeld, Donald (Rep.), R-IL (Box 292)
  - Ruritan National (Box 292)
  - Rushdoony, Rousas J. (Box 292)
  - Rusher, William A. (Box 292)
  - Ryker, Kenneth W. (Capt.), Fort Worth, TX (Box 292)
    [Former Director, Fort Worth Freedom Center Publisher, "Freedom File" See also the Group Research directory under Capt. Kenneth W. Ryker.]
  - Ryskind, Morrie, Sr. (Box 292)
  - Sabre Foundation (Box 292)
  - Sabrepen Syndicate (Box 292)
  - Safire, William (Box 292)
  - Sagebrush Rebellion (Box 292)
  - St. John, Jeffrey (Box 292)
  - St. Michael's Legion (Box 292)
  - St. Michael's Seminary (Box 292)
  - Strategic Arms Limitation Treaty (SALT) (Box 292)
  - Salvatori Foundation, The Henry and Grace, Los Angeles, CA (Box 292)
    [Founder and director, Henry Salvatori See also Henry Salvatori.]
  - Salvatori, Henry, Los Angeles, CA (Box 292)
    [Right-wing activist, especially concerned with anti-communism See also the Henry and Grace Salvatori Foundation and the Group Research directory under Henry Salvatori.]
  - Sanctuary Movement (Box 292)
  - Sandahl, Cliff (Box 292)
  - Sanger, Kenneth J. (Capt.) (Box 292)
  - Satterfield, John C. (Box 292)
  - Savage, Gus (Rep.), D-IL (Box 293)
  - Savarese, Melchoir F. R. (M.D.) (Box 293)
  - Save Our Constitution (Box 293)
  - Save Our Sovereignty (Box 293)
  - Saxon, O. Glenn (Box 293)
  - Save Our Sovereignty (Box 293)
  - Sayre, Charles R. (Box 293)
  - Scaife Foundation Scaife family (Box 293)
  - Schadeberg, Henry C. (Box 293)
  - Scheibla, Shirley (Box 293)
  - Scherer, Gordon H. (Rep.), R-OH (Box 293)
  - Scherle, William, R-IA (Box 293)
  - Schick Safety Razor Company (Box 293)
  - Schlafly, Daniel L. (Box 293)
  - Schlafly, John Fred, Jr. Alton, IL (Box 293)
    [Attorney, Firm of Eastman, Schlafly and Godfrey Former president, Defenders of American Liberties Husband of Phyllis Schlafly See also Defenders of American Liberties, Phyllis Schlafly, and the Group Research directory under John Fred Schlafly, Jr.]
  - Schlafly, Phyllis, Alton, IL (Box 293)
    [Former Research Director, Cardinal Mindszenty Foundation Wife of John Fred Schlafly, Jr. See also John Fred Schlafly, Jr., Cardinal Mindszenty Foundation, and the Group Research directory under Phyllis Schlafly, under "Strike from Space" (a book by Schlafly and Chester Ward), and under "The Gravediggers" (another book by Schlafly and Chester Ward).]
  - Schlafly, Phyllis, 1985- (Box 293)
  - Schlafly, Phyllis, 1982- (Box 294)
  - Schlafly, Phyllis, 1978- (Box 294)
  - Schlafly, Phyllis, 1972- (Box 294)
  - Schlafly, Phyllis (Box 294)
  - Schlamm, William S. East Wallingford, VT (Box 294)
    [Contributor to and editor of several right-wing publications See also the Group Research directory under William S. Schlamm.]
  - Schmidt, Emerson P. (Box 295)
  - Schmidt, Godfrey P. New York, NY (Box 295)
    [Attorney and right-wing activist See also the Group Research directory under Godfrey P. Schmidt.]
  - Schmitz, John G. (Box 295)
  - Scholastic Magazines, Inc. (Box 295)
  - Schuchman Memorial Foundation, Robert M. (Box 295)
  - Schuettinger, Robert Lindsay (Box 295)
  - Schuler, Ralph J. (Rev.) (Box 295)
  - Schultz, Harry D. (Box 295)
  - Schuyler, George (Box 295)
  - Schuyler, Philippa (Box 295)
  - Schuyler Memorial Foundation, Philippa (Box 295)
  - Schwarz, Fred C. (Dr.) (Box 295)
    [Founder and Former President, Christian Anti-Communism Crusade (CACC) See also Christian Anti-Communism Crusade (CACC) and the Group Research directory under Dr. Fred C. Schwarz.]
  - Scientific Information and Education (Box 295)
  - Scientology, 1984- (Box 295)
  - Scientology, 1975- (Box 295)
  - Scientology (Box 296)
  - Statewide Committees Opposing Regional Plan Areas (SCORPA) (Box 296)
  - Scott, John W. (Box 296)
  - Scott, Paul (Box 296)
  - Scott, Rudolf K. New Rochelle, NY (Box 296)
    [Former President, America's Future, Inc. See also America's Future, Inc. and the Group Research directory under Rudolf K. Scott.]
  - Scott, Robert L., Jr. (Gen.) (Box 296)
  - Schuchman, F. E. (Box 296)
  - Scott, Vernon (Box 296)
  - Scott, William L. (Sen.), R-VA (Box 296)
  - Scranton, William Warren (Box 296)
  - Scudder, Gene (Box 296)
  - Sears Roebuck and Company (Box 296)
  - Secrest, Charles (Box 296)
  - Secret Army Organization (Box 296)
  - Secular Humanism (Box 296)
  - Security and Intelligence Fund (and Foundation) (Box 296)
  - Self-Realization Fellowship (Box 296)
  - Selma Publications (Box 296)
  - Selvage and Lee Selvage, James (Box 296)
  - Seminars in Conservative Thought (Box 296)
  - Sennholz, Hans F. (Dr.), Grove City, PA (Box 297)
    [Professor of Economic, Grove City College, Grove City, PA See also the Group Research directory under Dr. Hans F. Sennholz.]
  - Sensing, Thurman, Nashville, TN (Box 297)
    [Former Vice-President, Southern States Industrial Council (SSIC) See also Southern States Industrial Council (SSIC) and the Group Research directory under Thurman Sensing.]
  - Sensitivity Training (Box 297)
  - Sentinel, The (Box 297)
  - Serbian National Committee (Box 297)
  - Sex Information and Education Council of the United States (SIECUS), 1971- (Box 297)
  - Sex Information and Education of the United States (SIECUS) (Box 297)
  - Serbian National Defense Council of America (SLOBODA) (Box 298)
  - Sertoma International (Box 298)
  - Seventh International Conference on the Unity of the Sciences (Box 346)
  - Shackelford, R.E. (Box 298)
  - Shadegg, Stephen C. (Box 298)
  - Shannon, George W. (Box 298)
  - Shasta County Chronicle (Box 298)
  - Shearer, William K. (Box 298)
  - Shearon Legislative Service Shearon, Majorie (Dr.) "Challenge to Socialism", Chevy Chase, MD (Box 298)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Dr. Marjorie Shearon and "Challenge to Socialism."]
  - Sheen, Fulton J. (Bishop) (Box 298)
  - Sheesley, Jay R. (Box 298)
  - Shell, Joseph C. (Box 298)
  - Shevchenko Memorial Committee of America, Inc. (Box 298)
  - Shipley, Carl (Box 298)
  - Shockley, William (Dr.) (Box 298)
  - Shofstall, Weldon P. (Prof.) (Box 298)
  - Shooters Committee on Political Education, Inc. (Box 298)
  - "Showers of Blessing" (Box 298)
  - Shuman, Charles B. (Box 298)
  - Siegel, Seymour (Prof.) (Box 298)
  - Siegrist, Robert R. (Box 298)
  - Sierra Club (Box 298)
  - Silent Majority Against Revolutionary Tactics (SMART) (Box 298)
  - Simon, William E. (Box 298)
  - Singlaub, John (Maj.Gen.) (Box 298)
  - Skousen, Joel (Box 298)
  - Skousen, Mark (Box 298)
  - Skousen, Max B. (Box 299)
  - Skousen, W. Cleon, Salt Lake City, UT (Box 299)
    [Anti-Communist crusader See also the Group Research directory under W. Cleon Skousen.]
  - Sloan Foundation, Alfred P. (Box 299)
  - Sluis, Joost (Dr.) (Box 299)
  - Small Business Economic Foundation (Box 299)
  - Small Business Legislative Council (Box 299)
  - Small Business Men of America, Inc. Los Angeles, CA (Box 299)
  - Smathers, George A. (Sen.), D-FL (Box 299)
  - Smears -- General (Box 299)
  - Smith, Alvin D. (Box 299)
  - Smith, Baker Armstrong (Box 299)
  - Smith, Bradford B. (Box 299)
  - Smith, Charles E. (Box 299)
  - Smith Foundation, The Elna M. (Box 299)
  - Smith-Kline Corporation (Box 299)
  - Smith, Luther A. (Box 299)
  - Smith, Raymond I. (Box 299)
  - Smoot, Dan, Dallas, TX (Box 299)
    [Founder and president, Dan Smoot, Inc. See also Broadcasting, Facts Forum, "Dan Smoot Report," and the Group Research directory under Dan Smoot and under Special Reports -- Voting Records and Indexes.]
  - Snowden Trust, John Bayard (Box 299)
  - Snowden, Robert B. Memphis, TN (Box 299)
    [Right-wing activist associated with the John Birch Society, Foundation for Economic Education, Inc., Christian Crusade, and Young Americans for Freedom among others. See also the Group Research directory under Robert B.Snowden.]
  - Snyder, M.G. (Box 299)
  - Snyder, Mike (Box 299)
  - Sobran, Joseph (Box 299)
  - Social Security (Box 299)
  - Snook, John (Box 299)
  - Socialist Workers Party Democratic Socialist Party (Box 300)
  - Society for a New Civilization (SFANC) (Box 300)
  - Society for French-American Affairs (Box 300)
  - Society for Individual Freedom (Box 300)
  - Society for Individual Liberty (Box 300)
  - Society for International Development (Box 300)
  - Society for Social Responsibility in Science (Box 300)
  - Society for the Christian Commonwealth (Box 300)
  - Society for the Family Man (Box 300)
  - Society for the Preservation of the White Race (Box 300)
  - Society for the Prevention of World War III (Box 300)
  - Society of Mayflower Descendants (Box 300)
  - Society to Exterminate Neo-Communist Harbingers (STENCH) (Box 346)
  - Sokolsky, George E. (Box 300)
    [See also American Jewish League Against Communism and Right Wing -- General.]
  - Soldiers of the Cross (Box 300)
    [See also Kenneth Goff.]
  - Sollitt, Kenneth W. (Rev.) (Box 300)
  - Sons of Liberty (Box 300)
    [See also New Patriot.]
  - Sons of the American Revolution (Box 300)
    [See also A. D. Rooke and Series 1 and 2 -- John Birch Society.]
  - Sontag, Frederick H. (Box 300)
  - Sorin-Hall, Inc. (Box 300)
  - Sound Dollar Committee, The (Box 301)
  - Sound Money Foundation (Box 301)
  - Sourwine, J. G. (Box 301)
  - South Africa (Box 301)
  - South Africa (Box 301)
    [See also American Society of African Culture and National Economic Council.]
  - South Bay Citizens Committee to Protest United Nations Atrocities in Katanga (Box 301)
  - South Dakota Taxpayers Association (Box 301)
  - Southard, Earl (Box 301)
  - "Southeast Asia Notebook, A" (Box 301)
  - Southern Association for the Restoration of States Rights (Box 301)
  - Southern Baptists (Box 301)
  - Southern Committee on Political Ethics (Box 301)
  - Southern Committee to Help Elect the Next President of the United States (Box 301)
  - Southern Committee to Uphold the Constitution (Box 301)
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund (Box 301)
  - "Southern Conservative, The", Washington and Lee University, Lexington, VA (Box 301)
  - Southern Education Conference (Box 301)
  - Southern Lunacy (Box 302)
    [See also Right Wing -- General, Inter-Citizens Committee of Alabama, Majority Citizens League of South Carolina, White Sentinel, Leander Perez, and Junior Chamber of Commerce.]
  - Southern National Party (Box 302)
  - "Southern Patriot, The" (Box 302)
  - Southern Patriots (Box 302)
  - Southern Regional Council, Inc. (Box 302)
  - Southern Research Institute (Box 302)
  - "Southern Review, The" (Box 302)
  - Southern States Industrial Council (SSIC) Financial, Nashville, TN (Box 302)
    [See also Group Research directory under Southern States Industrial Council.]
  - Southern States Industrial Council (SSIC), Nashville, TN (Box 302)
    [See also Southern States Industrial Council -- Financial, Southern States Industrial Council Bulletin, Thurman Sensing, and Sensing the News.]
  - "Southland Standard" (Box 302)
  - Sowell, Thomas (Box 303)
  - Spanel, Abraham N. (Box 303)
  - Spencer-Roberts and Associates (Box 303)
  - "Spiderweb" Charts (Box 303)
  - Spindale Mills, Inc. Spindale, NC (Box 303)
    [Former President, A. G. Heinsohn, Jr. See also A. G. Heinsohn, Jr. and Cherokee Textile Mills as well as the Group Research directory under Spindale Mills, Inc.]
  - Spirit of '76 House (Box 303)
  - Spirit of '76, Inc. (Box 303)
  - Spiritual Mobilization (Box 303)
  - "Spotlight" (Box 303)
    [See also Committee for Constitutional Government.]
  - Springer, Harvey (Rev.) (Box 303)
  - SPX Research Associates (Box 303)
    [See also Let Freedom Ring.]
  - Square Movement (Box 303)
  - Staar, Richard D. (Dr.) (Box 303)
  - Stahl, Steve (Box 303)
    [See also National Taxpayers Conference.]